Once a year, a race is held for old cars.
A lot of cars entered for this race last year and there was a great deal of excitement just before it began.
One of the most handsome cars was a Rolls -Royce Silver Ghost.
The most unusual car was a Benz which had only three wheels.
Built in 1885, it was the oldest car taking part.
After a great many loud explosions, the race began.
Many of the cars broke down on the course and some drivers spent more time under their cars than in them!
A few cars, however, completed the race.
The winning car reached a speed of forty miles an hour -- much faster than any of its rivals.
It sped downhill at the end of the race and its driver had a lot of trouble trying to stop it.
The race gave everyone a great deal of pleasure.
It was very different from modern car races but no less exciting.